# EDITO ABIS JR.

A pleasant day!

I wish to apply for any vacant position that fits my qualification. I am a vocational graduate and lots of experience and skills. I am 30 years old and willing to do multi tasking and humility to listen and learn. I am very much willing for any designation in your company.

## Work Experience

🖓 shahia food corps. | riyadh Saudi Arabia

salesman, service crew, stockman

Nov.2016 - Jan.2021

being a solo worker in coffee shop by performing task also to customers need and good service as well, always check the monitoring stocks and suggesting products to give sales target daily.maintain cleanliness inside/outside the shop. all utencils to be clean and proper handling and follow standard operating procedure.

# davao king chow food corps. | davao Davao Region Philippines

service crew

Mar. 2012 - Dec. 2013

ability to do multi-task and good perform, willing to listen and learn in all tasks to serve food with a smile and greet to customer.

## bachelor express inc. | davao Davao Region Philippines

ojt/welder

Oct.2010 - Dec.2010

teamwork and doing job well.

# digigraphix printshop | bislig Caraga Philippines

graphics design/layout

Jun.2021 - Present

good service and provide customer satisfaction by doing designs and layout in c omputer.



Email junpakswapo@gmail.co m

Phone 09709202279

Address p-9 St,Vincent Brgy, Baracatan Toril, Davao City davao Davao Region Philippines

#### Skills

welding

cook

computer layout

communication

### Languages

english,filipino,bisaya

\* \* \* \* \*

#### **Education**

#### OGREAT CENTER INC. | bislig Caraga Philippines

, WELDER

Sep.2010 - Nov.2010

ncll holder

### recaredo castillo college | bislig Caraga Philippines

highschool , Postgraduate Diploma

Jun.2004 - Mar.2008

#### mangagoy east elementary school

Jun.1998 - Mar.2004

#### **Custom Section**

REFERENCE:

Daniel degeñon

09451854582

baracatan toril davao city